[{"answer": "Well, Piers, it's a little difficult to tell.", "docId": "110314pmt", "aSentId": 75, "question": "And how significant is it on a wider level that we've now seen three of these in the last few days?", "qSentId": 74}, {"answer": "Well, it's a good question.", "docId": "110314pmt", "aSentId": 86, "question": "From what you are assessing with your more expert eye, how worried should we be here?", "qSentId": 85}, {"answer": "I'll tell you, first of all, Piers, as happening sometimes in disaster situations, we're having a hard time actually hearing you.", "docId": "110314pmt", "aSentId": 131, "question": "But in terms of this latest explosion, the nuclear explosion, how worried are people where you are about the possible radiation fallout here?", "qSentId": 130}, {"answer": "It seems very arbitrary.", "docId": "110314pmt", "aSentId": 158, "question": "But how arbitrary is that?", "qSentId": 157}, {"answer": "A very fluid situation obviously changing really by the hour, Piers.", "docId": "110314pmt", "aSentId": 183, "question": "How long is it going to be before other supplies get in here?", "qSentId": 182}, {"answer": "I think it depends who you talk to and where you are.", "docId": "110314pmt", "aSentId": 214, "question": "Is this commuting down to the people on the streets?", "qSentId": 213}, {"answer": "It's really impossible.", "docId": "110314pmt", "aSentId": 231, "question": "Is it still impossible to put any real gauge on it?", "qSentId": 230}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, Piers, thank you for having me on.", "docId": "110314pmt", "aSentId": 257, "question": "Gail, where do you possibly start with a disaster on the scale of the one that we are seeing in Japan?", "qSentId": 256}, {"answer": "CGOVERN: Well, it's an absolutely amazing the extent of damage and the visuals that we see on our screen for the last 72 hours.", "docId": "110314pmt", "aSentId": 267, "question": "I mean in terms of sheer volume of natural disasters we've seen in the last decade, how bad is this one from your perspective in terms of the work the Red Cross is needing to do to get to people there?", "qSentId": 266}, {"answer": "Well, we are very proud of the fact that 91 cents of every dollar that is donated to us goes to the relief efforts in the country that we're targeting.", "docId": "110314pmt", "aSentId": 278, "question": "How much of the money that goes to the Red Cross can be guaranteed to go straight to Japan and help there?", "qSentId": 277}, {"answer": "Well, right now food, shelter, medical supplies.", "docId": "110314pmt", "aSentId": 286, "question": "What is the priority for the Red Cross right now?", "qSentId": 285}, {"answer": "Well, I was in New York, of course.", "docId": "110314pmt", "aSentId": 319, "question": "Where were you?", "qSentId": 318}, {"answer": "Well, like you heard it, too, I suppose, through the -- through the TV news.", "docId": "110314pmt", "aSentId": 321, "question": "And how did you hear the news?", "qSentId": 320}, {"answer": "I just can't believe it.", "docId": "110314pmt", "aSentId": 323, "question": "Can you believe what you're seeing?", "qSentId": 322}, {"answer": "NO: Well, I was so scared.", "docId": "110314pmt", "aSentId": 332, "question": "What did it feel like?", "qSentId": 331}, {"answer": "That one was very -- pretty bad.", "docId": "110314pmt", "aSentId": 347, "question": "What was it look for you?", "qSentId": 346}, {"answer": "Because most of them are in Tokyo, and Tokyo was all right in a way.", "docId": "110314pmt", "aSentId": 356, "question": "Are they all OK?", "qSentId": 355}, {"answer": "Well, they're not violent people.", "docId": "110314pmt", "aSentId": 371, "question": "Is that very much the Japanese culture to react that way?", "qSentId": 370}, {"answer": "We're all together in spirit.", "docId": "110314pmt", "aSentId": 385, "question": "What would you say to them?", "qSentId": 384}, {"answer": "Well, as of now, I found that there's no definite funds -- foundation in Japan that we can send money to.", "docId": "110314pmt", "aSentId": 393, "question": "What is the best way for Americans in particular to help here?", "qSentId": 392}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110314pmt", "aSentId": 401, "question": "People are going to struggle to keep positive and helpful there, aren't they?", "qSentId": 400}, {"answer": "I think it's too far.", "docId": "110314pmt", "aSentId": 428, "question": "Can any country be ready for an attack of a natural disaster like this?", "qSentId": 427}, {"answer": "Well, the one thing that we do -- and this was after the Three Mile Island incident -- is the Nuclear Regulatory Commission and the Federal Emergency Management Agency required that each licensed operator conduct annual exercises, as well as drills.", "docId": "110314pmt", "aSentId": 441, "question": "How vulnerable are they to a similar perfect storm of earthquake and tsunami causing the kind of partial meltdowns that we're seeing?", "qSentId": 440}, {"answer": "Probably the one thing that you have heard time and time again from your guests is how resilient the Japanese population is.", "docId": "110314pmt", "aSentId": 446, "question": "What are the key lessons that you are learning watching what is happening in Japan, for a similar situation potentially one day happening in America?", "qSentId": 445}, {"answer": "Well, I agree with him that things have been improved since 9/11 and certainly since Katrina.", "docId": "110314pmt", "aSentId": 454, "question": "Do you agree with him, that we are in a relatively strong position in America?", "qSentId": 453}, {"answer": "Sure.", "docId": "110314pmt", "aSentId": 466, "question": "Do you have any way of predicting where the most likely places are that may suffer this thing?", "qSentId": 465}, {"answer": "Well, places like the central U.S. and places you may not think about, such as fault lines that occur in other parts of the country that don't have a lot of activity, but have had significant historical events, such as down in Charleston, South Carolina and other places.", "docId": "110314pmt", "aSentId": 472, "question": "Where are we talking about?", "qSentId": 471}, {"answer": "Well, it's going to be tough days ahead for the nuclear power industry.", "docId": "110314pmt", "aSentId": 513, "question": "What does this mean for the American nuclear energy project?", "qSentId": 512}, {"answer": "You never believe everything you're hearing, but we don't spy on the Japanese.", "docId": "110314pmt", "aSentId": 528, "question": "Or would you be suspicious the situation may be worse than we're told?", "qSentId": 527}, {"answer": "Well, if they can get hold of some of the material for dirty bombs, yes.", "docId": "110314pmt", "aSentId": 545, "question": "One of the issues here is that there will be terrorist organizations around the world looking at the vulnerability of these nuclear plants and looking at them as potential ultimate dirty bombs, won't they?", "qSentId": 544}, {"answer": "Number one, we have to recognize that we need to move toward more diverse sources of energy.", "docId": "110314pmt", "aSentId": 556, "question": "Governor Richardson, very quickly here, what would you say are the key lessons that America needs to learn in terms of its energy program from what we've seen in Japan in the last few days?", "qSentId": 555}, {"answer": "Piers, I've got to say that people are starting to get worried.", "docId": "110314pmt", "aSentId": 570, "question": "How worried are people on the ground there?", "qSentId": 569}]